digitaldesktopwallpaper.com 2013-12-21

# Digital Desktop Wallpaper - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**(1)       What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data: 

(a)      information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;

(b)      information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;

(c)      information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us including your name and email address;

(d)      information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters including your name and email address;

(e)      any other information that you choose to send to us through the various website forms or by email;

**(2)       Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on this website.    
Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.  Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website.  Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers.  The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information.  Google's privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.  For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.  This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites as usernames, passwords and other preferences would not be retained. If you are using the Firefox browser, you can refuse cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Options”, “Privacy” and unticking the “Accept cookies from sites” option. 

**(3)       Using your personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a)      administer the website;

(b)      improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;

(c)      enable your use of the services available on the website;

(f)      send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

(g)      send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(h)      send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you (where you have specifically agreed) by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);

(i)       provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

(j)     deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; 

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

**(4)      Disclosures**

We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

(a)      to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b)      in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c)      in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

(d)    to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**(5)      International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA. 

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

**(6)       Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

Data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

If you are a registered user you are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

**(7)       Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

**(8)       Your rights**

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.  Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email  at any time.  (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

**(9)       Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**(10)     Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

**(11)    Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to info[@]digitaldesktopwallpaper.com or by post to Digital Internet Limited, Bridge End House, Park Mount Avenue, Baildon, West Yorkshire, BD17 6DS.

Digital Internet Limited is registered in England and Wales, Company No. 06180687

This website privacy policy is based on a template created by [Website-contracts.co.uk](http://www.website-contracts.co.uk/) and distributed by [Website-law.co.uk](http://www.website-law.co.uk/)
